[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Following on the heels of Ben 's annoucement yesterday , I thought I 'd post that I have joined Google as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"joined\", does the state of the participant \"Google\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"SCALIA filed a dissenting opinion , in which THOMAS and ALITO joined .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"joined\", does the state of the participant \"THOMAS\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"n3td3v saw this story on BBC News Online and thought you should see it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the state of the participant \"story\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Huge amounts of money , which could have solved many social problems in this dysfunctional part of the world , are channeled into three concentric spheres supporting death and murder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"solved\", does the state of the participant \"amounts\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Texas Education Reform Caucus is made up of business leaders , educators , and elected officials dedicated to finding common sense approaches to improving education in Texas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"improving\", does the state of the participant \"education\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"And the President becomes a Dictator , unrestrained by anything in the Constitution , backed up by the Armed Forces , which would be entirely under his personal control .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"becomes\", does the state of the participant \"President\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yes , there is a 100 year - old Israeli - Arab conflict , but it is not where the main show is .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the state of the participant \"conflict\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Who knows how much they want me to pay to fix this thing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the state of the participant \"thing\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There is nothing wrong with a REAL negotiation , but nothing particularly helpful about generating one that s just for show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"generating\", does the state of the participant \"one\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My vet told me when a dog is vomiting a lot , it could be a sign of obstruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the state of the participant \"vet\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I believe he must have waited among the gorse bushes through which the path winds and struck him down as he passed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"struck\", does the state of the participant \"him\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bangs said his agency is still reviewing the decision .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"Bangs\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He warned water levels could still rise .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rise\", does the state of the participant \"levels\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"All he had to do for a complete victory was allow the military to go into Laos and Cambodia and finish off the shattered Communist forces .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"allow\", does the state of the participant \"military\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This BuzzMachine post argues that Google 's rush toward ubiquity might backfire -- which we 've all heard before , but it 's particularly well - put in this post .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"heard\", does the state of the participant \"we\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My family and I thank you !!!!!!!!!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thank\", does the state of the participant \"you\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It was incorporated as a city on May 26 , 1955 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"incorporated\", does the state of the participant \"It\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Previous reviewers said they were pushy and I can understand that , but I find the staff more helpful than anything else .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"understand\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I expected to pay for this service , but imagine my surprise when I received a bill for MORE than what I paid to have the original return prepared .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paid\", does the state of the participant \"what\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think he could 've done more to assuage my concerns by giving me concrete facts .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assuage\", does the state of the participant \"concerns\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Tangipahoa Parish sheriff 's deputy Christopher Blair Labat , 24 , was booked Tuesday on one count of aggravated rape and one count of crime against nature .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the state of the participant \"Labat\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the state of the participant \"laptop\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Once upon a time ( in 2001 , to be specific ) , the Coca - Cola corporation built a bottling plant in a small and remote Indian village in the state of Kerala .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the state of the participant \"plant\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In the words of my new accountant , THEY LET ME DOWN !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"LET\", does the state of the participant \"ME\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they fixed my garage doors in literally less than an hour .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the state of the participant \"doors\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The missile 's manufacturers state that one or two missiles could cripple a destroyer , and five missiles could sink a 20,000 ton ship .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sink\", does the state of the participant \"missiles\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My last son , was born in Northern Ontario ....\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the state of the participant \"son\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"What I know is that I have a close friend who's aunt disappeared in New Orleans .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"disappeared\", does the state of the participant \"aunt\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"On August 21st , 2009 I ordered furniture from Hickory Furniture Mart and contracted for HDS to deliver it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deliver\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have good sushi for a good price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"They\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Meditation has to do with what is called ideation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the state of the participant \"Meditation\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Last week , Federal District Judge Lynn Hughes in Huston , Texas , threw out Wilson 's two - decades old conviction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threw\", does the state of the participant \"conviction\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Brass melts at just under 2000 F which is a bright yellow heat , not red hot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"melts\", does the state of the participant \"Brass\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The lady at pet smart said 4 hours , but on places on the net it says 10 to 12 hours .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"hours\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i know you remember the bet .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the state of the participant \"i\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A state Senate committee is set today to start serving 16 subpoenas on electricity producers and officials who manage California 's energy grid to determine whether they acted in concert to manipulate energy prices .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"serving\", does the state of the participant \"subpoenas\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This action accelerated the utilities ' move toward bankruptcy and forced the governor to move the state into the power - buying business . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accelerated\", does the state of the participant \"action\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Our new lunar transportation system utilizes a unique architecture that will establish the equivalent of a two - way highway between the Earth and the Moon , \" Kistler told SPACE.com .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"utilizes\", does the state of the participant \"architecture\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"New Orleans mayor Ray Nagin said up to 80 % of the city was submerged , in some cases by waters 6 m ( 20 ft ) deep .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"submerged\", does the state of the participant \"%\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"By the late 1990s , Iraq had no nuclear or biological weapons program , and had destroyed its chemical weapons stockpiles .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the state of the participant \"program\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The difference is when the cat hisses , that means they are annoyed and they want the other cat to go away .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the state of the participant \"difference\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Louisiana 's Governor Blanco urged residents to spend Wednesday in prayer and assured them the crisis would eventually be overcome .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assured\", does the state of the participant \"them\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Orders for the deal to go ahead were given by the US Department of Defense .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"given\", does the state of the participant \"Orders\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I did the same thing that you did for christmas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the state of the participant \"thing\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We need to include all outstanding transactions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"include\", does the state of the participant \"transactions\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Damage estimates of more than $ 25 bn suggest it could be the US insurance industry 's most expensive natural disaster ever .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suggest\", does the state of the participant \"estimates\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I use Miracle Cloth , they 're fantastic , just do n't use fabric softener or dryer sheets when cleaning them , it ruins their \" grabbing \" ability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ruins\", does the state of the participant \"ability\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We tried 4 different style of donuts , they were all the same when it came to quality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tried\", does the state of the participant \"style\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Andreas Bechtolsheim built a microcomputer ; Vinod Khosla recruited him and Scott McNealy to manufacture computers based on it , and Bill Joy to develop a UNIX - based OS for the computer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the state of the participant \"microcomputer\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We came at around 730 and they close at 8 and wanted to try the specials but they were out for the day so I would say go way before they close .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"close\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I left you a voice mail on Friday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the state of the participant \"mail\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Across the United States , the northern edge of species ' range is expanding , \" she said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expanding\", does the state of the participant \"edge\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"During the session , he demanded to have my physical address , which I 've always kept private as I am enrolled in a witness protection program .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enrolled\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Restaurant on top was renovated , food was decent , price was way to high for Duluth for quality , new decor seems tacky\"\nQuestion: In the event \"renovated\", does the state of the participant \"Restaurant\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My brother said they only had full - auto and semiautomatic during Vietnam .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"brother\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed your recent e-mail but was sorry to hear about your dad .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoyed\", does the state of the participant \"e-mail\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Most experts believe China intends to develop a small space station of its own over the next several years .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"develop\", does the state of the participant \"station\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Even my PA i went to the other day said \" it must by comforting to have gone to a heart surgeon like him who will do nothing for you \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"PA\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The initial reservoir reports estimate reserves of 80 - 120 million barrels of sour crude and they estimate initial production to be 40,000 bpd starting in 1Q 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"estimate\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"That means making yourself known ; that means networking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"means\", does the state of the participant \"That\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"President Bush loves him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loves\", does the state of the participant \"him\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The millions who died in the Iran - Iraq war had nothing to do with Israel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the state of the participant \"millions\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think it s only fair that nowadays every town should provide at least one halal cafe or restaurant and hopefully one day every British catering establishment will be halal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A little birdie told me that you were checking into tickets for Seoul .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"checking\", does the state of the participant \"you\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Al - Sharq al - Awsat reports that a key eyewitness in the trial of Saddam Hussein for a 1982 massacre at Dujail has died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the state of the participant \"eyewitness\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a friend out in Chicago this week , and I am trying to remember the name of an awesome hibachi style restaurant i visited while out there a couple years ago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remember\", does the state of the participant \"name\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Plaster of Paris does two things\"\nQuestion: In the event \"does\", does the state of the participant \"things\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As of January 10 , 2005 , my source of income changed from The Mozilla Foundation to Google , Inc. of Mountain View , California .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"changed\", does the state of the participant \"source\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I remain convinced that if we can just get the facts in front of people they will modulate their approach .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"modulate\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The rapid victory during the first Gulf War cemented this perception .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cemented\", does the state of the participant \"perception\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Family owned and operated makes sure the atmosphere is relaxed and the food home - cooked with style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cooked\", does the state of the participant \"food\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We heard nothing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"heard\", does the state of the participant \"nothing\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I dropped the truck off in the morning and it was ready that afternoon .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dropped\", does the state of the participant \"truck\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Climate : Humans fuss , animals adjust\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adjust\", does the state of the participant \"animals\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They said that we were to be charged for this room regardless because we did not cancel within the 72 hours .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"They\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In Texas , BP shut its 460,000 barrels per day refinery and Marathon shut its 72,000 bpd plant .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shut\", does the state of the participant \"plant\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Is there any other way to communicate or do your friends only understand text .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"understand\", does the state of the participant \"text\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I need something reliable and good looking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the state of the participant \"something\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think I gained three pounds in my week long cruise .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gained\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I revised the language based on our discussions and added the language concerning interest which we had both previously approved .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"revised\", does the state of the participant \"language\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Police said Bernard confessed to detectives that he had sex with a young girl in November 2002 and admitted to knowing about sexual acts involving children and a dog that occurred at Hosanna Church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"involving\", does the state of the participant \"children\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The workers sped up and down the street with no mind to the small children playing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sped\", does the state of the participant \"workers\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Everything was done on a timely manner and things were cleaned and picked up every day when the crew was done .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"done\", does the state of the participant \"Everything\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have to tell you that I have n't had one and do n't want one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" He left a message for everyone to see ... maybe to God himself . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the state of the participant \"message\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Iran is encircled by Afghanistan , by the Gulf States , Iraq and the Moslem republics of the former Soviet Union .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"encircled\", does the state of the participant \"Iran\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"and around what time they eat each of their meals .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eat\", does the state of the participant \"each\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"jill allen finishes her cpa today and she and her friends are going to party .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finishes\", does the state of the participant \"allen\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" The governor believes it was the defining moment , when what was a mounting problem turned into an instant crisis , \" Maviglio said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"turned\", does the state of the participant \"what\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Founder Jack Smith got the idea of accessing e-mail via the web from a computer anywhere in the world .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the state of the participant \"idea\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they use them to look prickly .. would you try to eat a cactus [ if u had no knife ] i know i would nt .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eat\", does the state of the participant \"cactus\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"'' We have a very small number of forces in Shindand with a few helicopters , '' says Barno .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the state of the participant \"Barno\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called them for an estimate and they INSULTED ME WHEN I ASK THEM QUESTIONS .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"INSULTED\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i need to now get a job at house of pies b/c that is the only way to pay the bills .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the state of the participant \"i\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The next day i took it to 2 auto shops and they both told me the same thing , engine is junk .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the state of the participant \"i\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Events change everyday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the state of the participant \"Events\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Nobody thinks that there will be a lot of oil and gas in this part of the world , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"he\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had this ridiculous celebrity stylist from LA named Derrick .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It put hair on my chest and thanks to the owner s advice I invested vanguard , got myself a woman like Jerry , and became a republican .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"put\", does the state of the participant \"hair\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( I know , ignorant question ) Then why call them , or any other phonies ' Christians ' , even if they themselves claim the appellation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"claim\", does the state of the participant \"appellation\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But if -- there 's a painting on the wall in the Oval Office that shows a horseman charging up a steep cliff , and there are at least two other horsemen following .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shows\", does the state of the participant \"horseman\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They fixed the queso !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the state of the participant \"queso\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The sample includes our \" caveat \" , so it should be fine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"includes\", does the state of the participant \"caveat\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A 1971 evaluation called Bush \" an exceptionally fine young officer and pilot \" who \" continually flies intercept missions with the unit to increase his proficiency even further . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"increase\", does the state of the participant \"proficiency\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Police said Bernard confessed to detectives that he had sex with a young girl in November 2002 and admitted to knowing about sexual acts involving children and a dog that occurred at Hosanna Church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"confessed\", does the state of the participant \"Bernard\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Your fellow employees asked for everyone from Britney Spears to George Bush .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the state of the participant \"employees\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I live in London .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"live\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I hope you do n't change your mind about going to the wedding Sunday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the state of the participant \"mind\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Thanks to repeated deployments to Iraq and Afghanistan , recruiting is at an all - time low .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the state of the participant \"recruiting\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The mass murder happening right now in Sudan , where the Arab Moslem regime is massacring its black Christian citizens , has nothing to do with Israel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"massacring\", does the state of the participant \"citizens\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They did a vehicle wrap for my Toyota Venza that looks amazing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the state of the participant \"wrap\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You need either a filter for each device except the DSL modem , or a whole home filter which filters all the jacks , except the one which the DSL modem connects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filters\", does the state of the participant \"filter\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There is considerable evidence that it is developing both a long - range missile force and a range of weapons of mass destruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"developing\", does the state of the participant \"force\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"sorry , i left lou off of the message .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the state of the participant \"i\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There are several just off their beautiful beach .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the state of the participant \"several\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Plus , I work with Janet a lot so she may get some comfort from that , instead of having a lawyer she has n't dealt with initial it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dealt\", does the state of the participant \"she\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"President Bush pinched a few nerves yesterday with his choice of words :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pinched\", does the state of the participant \"Bush\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I see the merit in flowing with duality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"see\", does the state of the participant \"merit\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}]